http://www.sharehim.org/terms-of-use-and-privacy-policy

ShareHim Website Terms of Use and Privacy Policy
This website and its contents are provided by ShareHim, a department of the Carolina Conference of Seventh-day Adventists, Inc., on an “as is” basis. The information in this website is protected by all applicable law, including, but not limited to, trademark and copyright law.
By accessing this website, you agree 1) to be bound by these terms of use and privacy policy; 2) that you use this website at your own risk; 3) that you will not hold ShareHim or the Carolina Conference of Seventh-day Adventists, Inc. liable for any damages or injury (including, but not limited to, direct, indirect, actual, special, or consequential damages) that may result from the use of, or inability to use, this website, its contents, or any other websites linked to this website, including any damages or injury caused due to negligence; and 4) that these terms of use shall survive any removal or termination of this website.
ShareHim does not warrant or make any representations concerning the usability, accessibility, accuracy, or reliability of this website, its contents, or any other websites linked to this website. ShareHim makes no warranties, expressed or implied, regarding this website and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including, but not limited to, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement of intellectual property or other rights.
ShareHim collects various kinds of personal information in the course of its organizational and ministry activities, including through this website. This includes, but is not limited to, information supplied by users for the purpose of participating in ministry projects and accessing ministry tools, materials, coaching, and mentorship programs.
By providing information to ShareHim, you agree to allow ShareHim to use this information for organizational and ministry purposes at its sole discretion. ShareHim will exercise sole ownership and control of any information collected, including information collected on this website. ShareHim will not share this information with other parties except as needed to fulfill ShareHim organizational and ministry objectives. If you wish to opt out of this information sharing, you must contact ShareHim at
Be aware that due to the nature of ShareHim programs, opting out will likely result in the inability to be involved in these programs.
ShareHim reserves the right to update these terms of use and privacy policy at any time.
If you have questions about these terms of use and privacy policy, please contact ShareHim at
.
